

QUALIFICATIONS

Ongoing

BA IN ENGLISH LANGUAGE AND CULTURE

National Technological University, UTN (Argentina)

2010 - 2017

ENGLISH TEACHER

Teacher Training College "Dr. Bernardo Houssay" (Argentina)

2015 - 2017

SECONDARY SCHOOL DIPLOMA

E.E.S.T. N º 2 "Paula Albarracín de Sarmiento" (Argentina)

COURSES AND CERTIFICATIONS

Ongoing

WEB DEVELOPER

Coderhouse, digital school

2022

COPYWRITER

Coderhouse, digital school

2022

DIGITAL MARKETING AND E-COMMERCE

Ministry of Economic Production and Development

2005 - 2009

FRENCH, INTERMEDIATE (DELF B1)

National University of Quilmes (Argentina)

CONTACT

rlarrouyet@gmail.com



+ 54 9 11 31331136



/in/ramiro-larrouyet



RAMIRO LARROUYET

COPYWRITER -BILINGUAL TEACHER

ABOUT ME

I write academic essays and source bases doing thorough research. To improve it, I critique diverse material from feminist, gender, discursive, and narratological perspectives. I take part in international poetry and short-story competitions. Hypertertextual theory introduced me to the digital world. Thus, I decided to become a copywriter while learning about digital marketing and e-commerce, which at the same time led me to start a course on web development.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Copywriter

August 2022 - Ongoing

A Su Gusto

- Graphic and content design for a bakery shop.
- Copywriting techniques: BAB, 4U, 4P, PAS, PASTOR, AIDA, PASTOR.
- Content Creation Tools: Snapseed, Mojo, Canva, Blend, Miro.
- Collaborative work with a community manager.

English Teacher

June 2014 - Ongoing

Almafuerte, Bilingual School (Argentina).

- English Literature and Written Expression.
- Phonology, Grammar, Syntax, Morphology.
- · Project management and design.
- · Google Classroom, Moodle.

SKILLS

- Critical Thinking
- Research
- · Proofreading
- Detail-oriented
- Storytelling
- Leadership
- Bilingual
- Social Media: Linkedin, Instagram, Facebook
- Mercado Libre
- Tienda Nube
- Digital Marketing, E-commerce